(Raj:)It was gonna be like the old days.
The four of us hanging out...
(Howard:)...playing video games,
before you guys all got girIfriends.
(Raj:)Do you have any idea what it's like
to be the only one without a girIfriend?
(Raj:)Even if I get one someday...
(Raj:)...I'll still be the guy who got a girl
after Sheldon Cooper!
(Penny:)And that's how a girl makes a scene.
I'm sorry. You're right.
You deserve your weekend.
(Penny:)- Come on, Amy, let's go.
- What about the Science Center?
Oh, I'll let you hold my hair
while I throw up.
(Amy:)Rain check.
- I'm gonna go too.
- I'll miss you.
- But I'll miss you more.
- No, I'll miss you...
- Just leave.
Ahh. Okay, now,
this is the way it's supposed to be.
(Raj:)Men together, fighting the forces of evil.